

Guilherme Medical Device Engineer



27 February 1984



824 Des. Westphalen Str. Curitiba/Paraná/Brazil



+55 41 98802-8496



guipatriota@gmail.com

About me ——

Guilherme Patriota is an Electrical Engineer wich is in search for an opportunity to work in his areas of interest at Montreal and nearest cities. He has 9 years of experience working as Medical Devices Engineer in Brasil and has everything needed to make great and positive difference in your companny. He is maried without kids and are ready to immigrate to Montreal/QC/Canada.

Skills ——

Medical Device Certifications

Team Leadership

French

English

Electronics

Medical Equipments

(*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

Interests

High technologies; R&D; Medical Equipments; Fixing things; New knowleges

Education

2013-2016	MBA in Healthcare Improvements into medical equipments maintenance.	FGV/Brazil
2009-2011	M.Sc. Electrical Engineer AI with electronics and telecommunications.	UFPR/Brazil
2002-2006	B.Sc. Electrical Engineer Electronics and telecommunications.	UFPR/Brazil
2004-2004	B.Sc. Electrical Engineer Sandwitch degree in Electrical Engineer - Electronics	ENSPS/France

Complementary Studies

2015	1st Clinical Engineering Club Meeting BCH/Brazil	4h
2015	1st Workshop for Medical Engineer Hospital das Nações/Brazil	4h
2020	Knowledge discovery in database and datamining UFPR/Brazil	60h
2020	Data Science Fundamentals Course in Curitiba Aldeia Coworking/Brazil	32h
2020	Introduction to computer programming using python MITx	9 weeks
2020	AI fundamentals. Data Science Academy	8h
2020	Datascience 2.0. Data Science Academy	8h

Experience

since 2020

2019 2020

2018-2020	Build, repair end configur 3d printer and make and print 3d modelis spare parts.	ng
2017-2018	Medical Equipments Engineer Santa Casa Hospi Maintain and repair medical equipments and manage technicit teams.	
2015-2017	Medical Equipments Engineer Curitiba's Red Cross Hospi Maintain and repair medical equipments and manage technicit teams.	
2012-2014	Medical Equipments Engineer Vitoria Hospi Maintain and repair medical equipments and manage technicit teams.	

Develop eletronics and software for new 3d printers and other prod-

Boa Impressão 3D

Hardware and Software Developer

ucts. Manage the assembly line.

Other information

Disponibility

I am interested to immigrate to Canada as soon as possible and I am ready to pay for my expenses but I will need a job offer for my documentations.

Other Skills and Interests

Python and C++ Programming; Data Science; 3D Printing; Cryptocurencies; LaTex programming; Artificial Inteligence; PMBOK; Automation;